[Music]
well
well well
after all that the running
the hiding i had to kill
every single one of your friends
but somehow every time you seem to be
the one
that got away but now look at us
you're here you've fallen
right into my lap
[Laughter]
i am going to enjoy
you don't want to blow the moment do you
no what a waste that would be especially
when you've got a beautiful
brand new axe just like this one
[Music]
did you cut your tongue
why don't you take your hand away from
your mouth
[Music]
you cut your tongue didn't you
why would you lick your axe you're cool
itch cool no no it's not cool
shut up
what why would it make it so sharp you
know it's an
do you axe any like aloe or neosporin or
something
for your mouth i don't know
i might have some in my car um
could you go get it oh
sure yeah
yeah yes i will and we'll go get that
for you
wait wait you're gonna come back right
yes
oh man
you